### Marwan Bukhori | Back-End Developer

marwanbukhori.dev@gmail.com | 013-596-1559 | Puchong, Selangor www.linkedin.com/in/marwanbukhori/ | github.com/marwanbukhori | marwanbukhori.com

## Summary

Dedicated backend developer with passion and strong desire to expand knowledge across multiple different domains within the tech industry. Experience in pinnacle of Point of Sales (POS) Fuel Retail System whose clients are Petronas, Shell and BH Petrol. I have proficiency in tech stacks as in *NestJS Laravel Typescript YAML Vue MySQL REST HTML CSS Tailwind*. As well, have proficiency in *AWS Cloud, Docker* and a *Certified Kubernetes Administrator*. Testing tools include implementing *Jest* and *Cypress* for unit/e2e Test. Knowledgeable in Monolith, Microservices and Serverless architecture, Multi-tenant databases and design patterns such as Domain-Driven Design and Monorepo. Have personal exposure in other programming languages such *Python Django Flutter*. Love to feed on my curiosity on new exposure and knowledge gain along the path. Free to migrate to any location as per required.

### **Experience**

SILENTMODE SDN. BHD. 2024 - Present

Software Engineer

Aug 2024 - Present

- A sister company to Terato Tech, absorbed due to having experience handling and developing RONPOS
- Currently working under RONPOS core team which focus on E-Invoice System (EIS) under RONPOS development for clients such as Shell and BH Petrol
- Knowledgeable in monorepo pattern using Vue3 frontend and NestJS backend with Typescript. EIS acts as
  one of NestJS microservice which interacts with RONPOS core platform
- Apply dockerized container concept using *Docker* and developed using *LocalStack* for local AWS environment development
- Contributed to development of AWS services with AWS Kinesis, Lambda, SQS, DynamoDB, CloudWatch etc on EIS based on serverless architecture plan
- Troubleshooted, monitored incident management by investigation logs on the CloudWatch and Sentry.
- Implemented unit and e2e testing using tools like Jest and Cypress
- Have experience in YAML, deployed features to staging, UAT and production environment using the Gitlab CICD pipeline
- Currently one of maintainers for the *EIS* project repository, solely responsible for development, fixing of issues and enhancement, also deployment release
- Experience in executing Linux operations to monitor and troubleshoot application performance in Ubuntu and Windows hosted server environments using *MeshCentral*

TERATO TECH SDN. BHD. 2022 - 2024

Junior Software Engineer

Feb 2023 - Aug 2024

- Currently working in the Site Business Operation (SBO) Team for *RONPOS*, a POS fuel system with clients such as Shell and BH Petrol. Previously on *SENTINEL* Team, which is a POS fuel system dedicated to Petronas.
- Handle support/defect/bug tickets for any features and reports that fall into SBO which is the most major module in RONPOS.
- Work alongside senior developers and teams to contribute to the development of new features and functionalities in a dedicated web application.

### Marwan Bukhori | Back-End Developer

marwanbukhori.dev@gmail.com | 013-596-1559 | Puchong, Selangor www.linkedin.com/in/marwanbukhori/ | github.com/marwanbukhori | marwanbukhori.com

- Proactively learn new knowledge and tools needed to deliver for any task assigned and constantly engage
  with team members to solicit feedback, addressing critical issues, or to offer assistance as needed
- Enhance current system flow to increase user experience, like dynamic input calculation approach for users to generate reports instead of just choosing from the options
- Developed reports which involved handling *SQL* queries from tables having up to one billion rows and plus. This involves doing database indexing, and requires more efficient *SQL* query
- Always on to improve code readability and structure by learning from others' code and combining knowledge gain everyday
- Daily stack includes *HTML*, CSS, *Laravel*, *Vue*, *VueX*, NestJS *Microservices*, *Docker*, *AWS*, *MySQL*, *Postgres*, *REST* api and more

## Internship Software Developer

Sept 2022 – Feb 2023

- Convert figma designs into multiple working mobile app screens by picking up *React Native* for in-house app development
- Setup API endpoints and response interfaces using Typescript types and use RTK query for handling API
- Managed to develop a Minimum Viable Product (MVP) of the app which mostly required front end skills using *Nativewind CSS*, React Native and Redux for state management
- involved in backend Laravel (which act as CMS), developed bulk import excel file feature which involves integration of Google Sheet. Aim to facilitate creating new objects/rows by just pasting a google sheet link equipped with template. Users fill in the excel and import it by submitting the link
- Take initiative to gather new tasks and resolve ongoing bug fix issues on the backend side and suggest improvements for existing flow
- Mobile stacks include React Native Typescript Nativewind RTK Query
- Backend CMS stacks include HTML CSS Laravel Livewire MySQL AlpineJS

### Education

### **Universiti Kebangsaan Malaysia**

2019 - 2023

Bachelor of Software Engineering (Information System)

- Graduated First Class with CGPA 3.76
- 5x Dean List Award Recipient
- JPA Scholar
- EXCO Multimedia of I-Business Group
- Mentor Guru Cemerlang in Programming Subject

### Marwan Bukhori | Back-End Developer

marwanbukhori.dev@gmail.com | 013-596-1559 | Puchong, Selangor www.linkedin.com/in/marwanbukhori/ | github.com/marwanbukhori | marwanbukhori.com

### **Skills**

## **Backend Development**

NestJS Laravel PHP Typescript Livewire Django MySQL REST

### **Frontend Development**

Vue Typescript HTML CSS Tailwind CSS

## **Mobile Development**

Dart Flutter React Native

#### **Tools**

Docker Kubernetes Jest Cypress

### **Others**

Microservices, Monolith, Serverless Architecture Domain Driven Design Git AWS Cloud Services

### Certifications

## **Certified Kubernetes Administrator**

Issued by The Linux Foundation

## **Certified DevOps Foundation**

Issued by CCSD Council Europe

# Program Bimbingan Pembangunan Aplikasi Mobile

**Dengan Flutter Selama 4 Minggu** 

Issued by Taming Tech Sdn. Bhd.

## Bengkel Pembangunan Aplikasi Mudah Alih Flutter

Issued by Mobile App Development Club UKM

### **Learn CSS**

Issued by YouAccel Training and Udemy

### **Learn HTML**

Issued by YouAccel Training and Udemy

### References

Will provide if needed.